dvor.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy

Dvor is a division of OpticsPlanet, Inc. (Dvor and OpticsPlanet, Inc. are collectively referred to as "Dvor"). Dvor respects consumer privacy and works to safeguard your personal information, while complying with United States Federal and State laws and regulations. We are dedicated to providing you with the superior customer experience that you know and expect from Dvor. We view your privacy as an important component of your customer experience and ensure that your personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. By visiting or using Dvor, you acknowledge and agree that your use signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy.

## What is your General Privacy Policy?

Dvor protects your privacy. We share only that data required to provide you with a superior customer experience and that data required in the ordinary course of business, including information necessary for validation of credit transactions, verification of identity, shipping and billing addresses, tracking orders and visitors, obtainment of payment, marketing and merchandising efforts, improvement of your consumer experience, and other data as described in this Policy.

## What Personal Information do you Collect?

We collect personal information about you to improve your experience at Dvor. If you choose to use Dvor or participate in the registration process, you consent to the transfer and storage of your personal information. This information allows us to provide you with a consumer experience tailored to your needs.

We may request or retain the following for our database:

  * Your Full Name
  * Bill-To Information, Ship-To Information, and Addresses
  * Contact Information, including Email Address and Telephone Number
  * Birthday Information
  * Financial and Credit Information, as needed
  * Order Information
  * Information Specific to Individual Customers
  * Export Compliance and Domestic Compliance Certifications
  * End Use, End User, Country of Ultimate Destination Information
  * Any Information Required by the U.S. Department of State or the U.S. Department of Commerce for Export Licensing
  * Identifications or Employers, as needed to verify law enforcement, military or professional status
  * Internet Protocol Address
  * Individual Customer Preferences
  * Gender
  * Browser Information

Additionally, certain features may require the collection of additional information. We will notify you if additional information is required, such as your product or brand preferences or additional information on your demographics. You are not required to provide Dvor with any personal information. However, if you fail to provide certain information, you may be unable to use certain features or purchase items through Dvor.

When you invite a friend or contact to join Dvor, you provide his/her email address. Dvor stores this information to provide you with appropriate credits per our policy. Email addresses will be used for purposes of invitations to join Dvor and will permit the recipient to unsubscribe to future emails.

## How do you use My Information?

Dvor is a division of OpticsPlanet, Inc. We share your information with our parent subsidiaries, divisions and affiliates to provide you with advertising targeted to your interests, inform you of special events at Dvor, improve your user experience at Dvor, and permit you to purchase items tailored to your needs. 

## Do you Maintain a Database?

Dvor maintains a private customer database for its own company use and marketing efforts. If you do not wish to receive our newsletters or marketing emails, you may request deletion of your address via the removal instructions available in the newsletter or marketing emails. Upon the completion of your registration with Dvor, you have opted to receive email communication and newsletters from OpticsPlanet, Inc. and all divisions of OpticsPlanet, Inc., including Dvor.

## Can I access and/or edit my Personal Information?

Dvor  allows registered users to access the following information for updates and viewing:

  * Your Full Name
  * Bill-To Information, Ship-To Information, and Addresses
  * Contact Information, including Email Address and Telephone Number
  * Financial and Credit Information
  * Order Information
  * Individual Preferences

As Dvor changes and adds new features, this list may change.

You may also edit your preferences for email and other communications, by logging into your account. Please note that your contacts may still send invitations for Dvor to you from email addresses that were not previously identified in our system.

## How do I Consent to Dvor's Policies?

By visiting, registering or doing business with Dvor, you give consent to the implementation of the privacy policy and all policies set forth herein. By denying access to any required personal information for the completion or verification of registration or a transaction, or refusing  participation in live chat, forums, testimonials, reviews, feedback forms, or other information required to communicate or conduct business with Dvor, you may surrender the ability to transact with Dvor.

## What Personal Data may be Shared or Disclosed?

Dvor does not sell or share your personal information with other non-affiliated companies or persons. However, under the following circumstances, and as permitted by law, we may be required to share your personal information:

  * Dvor provides information as needed to respond to any subpoenas, court orders, legal process, enforceable governmental requests, legal claims or to comply with any applicable laws or regulations. Dvor reserves the right to share your personal information to exercise any legal rights or to defend against any legal claims.
  * Dvor shares information as may be required to further law enforcement investigations, to prevent illegal activity and fraudulent activity, and to assist in taking action against illegal activity. Additionally, Dvor shares information, as permitted by law, to preserve the reputation and integrity of Dvor, to prevent any harm to rights or property of our customers or Dvor and to address any issues arising out of or related to fraud.
  * Dvor is a division of OpticsPlanet, Inc., and your personal information may be shared with OpticsPlanet, Inc. and all of its divisions. If Dvor is acquired by or merges with any other company or entity, your personal information may be transferred to any parent companies, subsidiaries, affiliates or successors.
  * Dvor may share information to address security, technical or customer service issues or enforce any policies or terms and conditions of our websites or transactions.
  * Dvor may provide your information to our trusted service providers who work under confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements or assist with our business operations, including the maintenance and operation of Dvor. Such companies may support our effective and innovative marketing techniques or aid in services necessary for fulfillment or completion of orders.
  * Dvor may share information as needed for the processing, tracking and fulfillment of any orders, as well as to collect fees and resolve any payment issues. Additionally, Dvor may share information to track email invitations sent or calculate credit information.
  * Dvor may share specific order information such as first and last names and shipping addresses as needed for the processing, tracking and fulfillment of any orders placed with Third-Party sellers on the Dvor Marketplace.
  * Dvor may use personal information to provide you with important marketing or promotional notices and to improve our marketing efforts or website design.
  * Dvor shares information with other third parties when necessary to improve your consumer experience. Please note that personal information includes any information that can be used to identify a specific person, not anonymous information about a user. 
  * Dvor may aid or facilitate with your ability to share personal information via social media or networking websites, only at your option.
  * Dvor may provide aggregate statistics about the use of Dvor to third parties, but these statistics do not include individual personal information.

Please note that personal information includes any information that can be used to identify a specific person, not anonymous information about a user.

Dvor does not disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.

## How do you Protect Credit Data?

Dvor reserves the right to exchange individual credit data and credit experience as any other company or organization may do in the ordinary course of business. Exchanging information may be necessary for payment processing, verification purposes and fraud prevention, etc. This policy protects the order process on the Internet, promotes individual responsibility and protects consumers. Dvor takes necessary measures to ensure your credit data is secure and only shared with authorized persons or entities.

## Is my Personal Information Secure?

We are committed to handling your information in a safe and secure manner. We follow commercially reasonable efforts to protect the security and integrity of personal information collected during your registration process and through use of Dvor.

When you register with Dvor, you select a username and password for privacy and security purposes. You should always protect your password appropriately. Always log out of Dvor after you have finished using your account.

## Is your Ordering Process Secure?

Dvor ensures the safe transmission of your personal information during the ordering process. We make certain that our ordering process is up-to-date, secure and capable of protecting your personal information.

## Is any Information Provided Automatically?

When you visit Dvor, we may receive information about your visit automatically through data collection tools and methodologies used in the ordinary course of business. These tools enhance the quality of our service and provide you with a user-friendly experience. Further, some email communications may allow us to confirm receipt so that we can customize emails according to your interests.

## What if I am referred to another Site or Service?

We may provide links to Sites or Services outside of the Dvor site for your reference or use. Dvor may not have any affiliation with these sites or services and you should review the privacy policies associated with these sites or services. Dvor is not responsible for the privacy policies of external sites. Please see the following privacy policies for information about checkout options: [PayPal](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?country.x=US&locale.x=en_US).

## What are Your Practices regarding Children's Privacy?

Only those individuals 18 years of age or older are authorized to use Dvor. Dvor is not designed for use by those individuals under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, please do not submit any personal information to Dvor.

## Is this Policy Subject to Change?

Dvor reserves the right to change this privacy policy as needed. Please check back with us for any updates. By continuing to visit or use Dvor after changes are made, you continue to assent to the Privacy Policy as posted.
